### SUBRAMANIAN KRISHNAMURTHY

Address: D/104, Pavandham Society, Samta Laxmipura Road, Vadodara, Gujarat

-390023

Date of Birth: 20th June, 1986.

 $\hbox{E-mail address: skskrishna 84@gmail.com}$ 

Contact No: +91 9820569326, 9082750667

Languages Proficiency: English, Tamil, Hindi and Gujarati.

### **OBJECTIVE**

♦ To achieve stability and valuable experience in an organization and adapt to its culture, which will be instrumental in accomplishment of, strategic objectives entrusted to me.

 Contribute to long-term growth and progress of the organization by working sincerely towards such path.

### **EDUCATION**

YEAR OF	Course	INSTITUTION
PASSING		
2008	B.com	MS University, Vadodara
2005	HSC general stream	Baroda High School, Vadodara
2003	SSC	Sabari Vidyalaya, Vadodara

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Intelenet Global Services**

Designation – Customer Support Associate from August 2012 to February 2015

- Handling consumer complaints and escalations involving close to 4000 products through 60% chat, 20% email and 20% voice calls.
- Preparing timely excel sheets and reports.
- Monitoring complaints and doing follow ups.
- Email the consumers and clients regularly about complaint progress.
- Preparing presentations for the clients during their visit.

#### **WNS Global Services**

# Designation - Operations Associate for British Airways since February 2015 – February 2017

- Worked for British Airways.
- Handled all the queries and complaints of customers through 50% email and 50% chat.
- Ensure follow up of complaints and ensure it is escalated if the gravity is higher.
- Monitor the booking status and coordinate with pretravel team to ensure prompt resolution of complaints.
- Liasoning with refunds team for faster process of refunds.

### **Runwal group**

## Designation- Senior Client relationship management executive from March 2017 to April 2020

- Meet the clients and address all after sales queries and issues
- Prepare a comprehensive list of clients nd coordinate with other ancillary teams to ensure smooth processing.
- Give presentations to the in house team as well as intermediaries regarding the aftersales work flow structure.

### **Kanan International Private Limited**

## Designation- Senior Executive Back-office operations March 2022 till present

- Speak with college representative and 3rd party to get the backlogs of application or any other pending issues resolved.
- Query the case with agents and Relationship managers to understand the exact requirements of student.
- Communication with colleges and universities through emails, webforms, contact forms or portals for offer letters, deferrals, fee extensions, login issues, registration issues, address, name or other data changes
- Work on sheets comprising different colleges.

### **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

- Interested in writing blogs on several topics.
- Travelling to beaches and hill-stations.
- Interested in watching good English news channels.
- Passion for cycling and automobiles.
- Research on newer technologies in vehicles.
- Have a natural flair for encyclopedia.

### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

Completed a certificate course in Basic, MS-Office and Tally.

- Considerable proficiency in preparing Power-point presentations and M.S. Word Reports
- Certificate in GCC typewriting

### **EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

- Participated in Elocution Competitions at school.
- Participated in an Elocution competition at M.S. University and stood second.

### **OTHER ATTRIBUTES**

- Perseverance.
- Strong memory power
- Excellent verbal and written communication skills.
- Significant cordiality and politeness.
- ♦ Flexibility
- ♦ Good presentation skills.
- Unique ability to remember on which day a particular date falls.